math2.org 2005-04-03

# Math2.org Privacy Policy

The following statements pertain only to the pages on the Math2.org web server (www.math2.org) and pages on the former Dave's Math Tables web site (www.sisweb.com/math). Math2.org is in the process of transferring its resources off the www.sisweb.com/math site and onto the www.math2.org server; therefore, both locations must currently be mentioned here. These statements do not apply to pages residing on other servers that Math2.org links to or even those sites what have a relationship with Math2.org. 

  * We respect your and your child's privacy and urge everyone to check for a privacy policy on any site that requests personal information. 
  * We do not sell or disseminate personally identifiable information about site visitors to third parties, except to report site abuse. 
  * We do not send or promote junk e-mail (spam). 

**Exceptions:**

  * We reserve the right to collect data on users for strictly internal use, such as in maintaining access and error logs. This is common practice for improving site performance and recording site abuse. 
  * On the message boards, personally identifiable information (such as e-mail addresses) will be disseminated if the user explicitly chooses to post it. Publicly posting one's e-mail address is discouraged and is not necessary because of the "message forwarding" option, which achieves the same function. 
  * We do at times post web site addresses and sometimes contact information of web site administrators for purposes of linking to web resources and generating external traffic. All requests for address removal will be honored. 

For general information on Internet privacy and safety issues see
